A Guide to the Stanley A. Huffman, Jr., Papers, 1917-1991
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Stanley A. Huffman, Jr., Papers, 1917-1991
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1991-056
11.2 cu. ft. 8 boxes
The collection consists of professional papers compiled over the course of Huffman's career at Virginia Tech (1971-1991).
Huffman, Stanley A., Jr.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Stanley A. Huffman, Jr. Papers were donated to Special Collections in 1991.
Biographical Note
Over the course of his extensive career, Stanley A. Huffman, Jr. was a school teacher, administrator, professor, consultant, and producer of television programs for education with a particular emphasis on use of technology and media. He held degrees from Virginia Polytechnic Institute (now Virginia Tech) and the University of Virginia. From 1971 to 1987, he served as the director of the Learning Resources Center and from 1987 to 1991 he was the director of Distance Learning at Virginia Tech. Huffman died in 1993.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of professional papers compiled over the course of Huffman's career at Virginia Tech (1971-1991). A majority of materials are group in subject files. Other types of materials include correspondence, administrative paperwork, and presentation, conference and research files. In addition, the collection contains the manuscript for Huffman's 1969 book, Instructional Media.
Arrangement
The collection is in its original order. For the most part, folders contain various subject files and materials from presentations and publications.
Index Terms
Persons:
Huffman, Stanley A., Jr.
Corporate Names:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State Univer. Learning Resource Center.; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. Distant Learning.
Subjects:
Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Local Subjects:
Faculty; University Archives
Contents List
- Right to die, 4/26/91 (Box-folder 1-1)
- Logistics: The new look (Box-folder 1-2)
- Composite Teleconference (Box-folder 1-3)
- Fair Housing Act of 1988 (Box-folder 1-4)
- Apple Series - Mac in the classroom, Jan 24, Feb 21, March 21, & April 25 (Box-folder 1-5)
- Hubble Lighting Meeting (Box-folder 1-6)
- Racial Harassment Oct 5, 1990; Campus Security Nov 15, 1990; NUTN/Pendergrass (Box-folder 1-7)
- Electricity Nov. 1990 (Box-folder 1-8)
- Why Graduate School, Oct. 30 1990 (Box-folder 1-9)
- N.T.U Uplink, Oct 16 & 17, 1990 (Box-folder 1-10)
- National Quality Forum, Oct. 2, 1990 (Box-folder 1-11)
- The Power of Caring, Sept 30, 1990 (Box-folder 1-12)
- Communication Aids Aids & Devices, May 10, 1990 - June 7,1990 (Box-folder 1-13)
- Marriott & You-CEC 10/3/90 (Box-folder 1-14)
- Man, Energy & The environment, Oct 3, 1990 (Box-folder 1-15)
- Black Fraternitiees & Sororities; CEC RearAud, Nov 28, 1990 (Box-folder 1-16)
- Europe '92 CEC, Feb 22 & March, 1990 (Box-folder 1-17)
- Dept. of Youth, May 7, 1990 (Box-folder 1-18)
- Apple Education TV Series, April 18, 1990 - May 16, 1990 (Box-folder 1-19)
- AECT Teaching & Technology Teleconference, March 14, 1990 (Box-folder 1-20)
- AECT Teleconference, March 14, 1990 (Box-folder 1-21)
- How to do a newsletter that gets read (Box-folder 1-22)
- Governor's School Teleconference-CEC, March 25-26, 1990 (Box-folder 1-23)
- Black Managers Forum; Downlinked Roanoke Grad. Center, Jan 17, 1990 (Box-folder 1-24)
- An Apple A Day: The Pesticide Dilemma, November 29, 1989 (Box-folder 1-25)
- Food Fights: How to decide about diet & disease, April 19, 1990 (Box-folder 1-26)
- Kodak Teleconference, Oct 5 & Nov 9, 1989 (Box-folder 1-27)
- Educom '89, October 6, 1989 (Box-folder 1-28)
- KTCA-Minn, 9/12/89 (Box-folder 1-29)
- President's Global Warming Teleconf (Box-folder 1-30)
- NUTN Teleconf; Hypermedia Interactive Avenues of Info, May 4, 1989 (Box-folder 1-31)
- NUTN Teleconf Double Jeopardy - Environmental Production, 5/23/89 (Box-folder 1-32)
- ABC's Advanced Business Television 2:30-4:30 Eastern, May 9, 1989 (Box-folder 1-33)
- Detergents In Depth '89 Conf Rm B-CEC, 5/11/89 (Box-folder 1-34)
- Interactive Telecommunication in Iowa, May 25, 1989 (Box-folder 1-35)
- Basketball TeleClinic Coverage, 4/1/89 (Box-folder 1-36)
- Nutrition Science: Fallacies, Fads & Facts, Spring, 1989 (Box-folder 1-37)
- Nutrition & Health Issues: Information/Misinformation, 3/13/89 (Box-folder 1-38)
- Black Issues in Higher Education, Feb 1, 1989 (Box-folder 1-39)
- Home Diagnostics Tests Teleconf VCU CEC, March 15, 1989 (Box-folder 1-40)
- AECT Teleconference "Star Schools," 2/3/89 (Box-folder 1-41)
- "Myths, Models, & Realities," Feb 7, 1989 (Box-folder 1-42)
- Autocad Release 10 & Autolisp (1810) Animal Set Bldg, Nov 30 - Dec 1 (Box-folder 1-43)
- Acquaintance/Date Rape Prevention NUTN, Feb 2, 1988 (Box-folder 1-44)
- Teleconference/Short Course "Logistics Engineering" (Box-folder 1-45)
- Satelite Comm Short Course, Fall, 1988 (Box-folder 1-46)
- High Temperature Superconductor, October 26, 1988 (Box-folder 1-47)
- Succesfull Aging Dairy Council Teleconference, Nov 1, 1989 (Box-folder 1-48)
- Discovery Lecture Series, 11/15/89 - 2/15/90 (Box-folder 1-49)
- "AIDS in the college community," Nov 16, 1989 (Box-folder 1-50)
- Artificial Intelligence, 11/10/88 (Box-folder 1-51)
- Dinosaurs Teleconference, 11/9/88 (Box-folder 1-52)
- Kodak Teleconference (Box-folder 1-53)
- "Stop that thief" Teleconference NUTN (Box-folder 1-54)
- Preventing Adolescent Pregnancy CEC, 10/31/88 (Box-folder 1-55)
- "Sexual Harassment on Campus" NUTN, October 21, 1988 (Box-folder 1-56)
- Assessment to improve student learning & development NUTN, Oct 7, 1988 (Box-folder 1-57)
- Alcohol A Special Report 8:30 Pm, 10/18/88 (Box-folder 1-58)
- Visa interface strategies '88 Computer Science Resource Consortium, October 5 &12 1988 (Box-folder 1-59)
- E.I.T, Fall of 1989 (Box-folder 1-60)
- E.I.T (3), Spring 1989 (Box-folder 1-61)
- E.I.T - 2 (Box-folder 1-62)
- EIT Exam Norris Bell, Feb - April 1988 (Box-folder 1-63)
- Emerging Technologies in Modern Language Instruction, 5/10/88 (Box-folder 1-64)
- Marketing Higher Education to Adults, 5/10/88 (Box-folder 1-65)
- AIDS Conference (Box-folder 1-66)
- NUTN Teleconference - Zallen, April 14, 1988 (Box-folder 1-67)
- Racism on Teleconf NUTN, 3/22/88 (Box-folder 1-68)
- CNS Drugs: Where are we?, 3/16/88 (Box-folder 1-69)
- The Electronic Campus Teleconference, 3/23/88 (Box-folder 1-70)
- Supported Employment Teleconf CEC, 2/2/88 (Box-folder 1-71)
- "Update on Interactive Learning" CEC, 12/3/87 (Box-folder 1-72)
- NUTN Teleconference "Every building must have an exit" (Box-folder 1-73)
- CRD/League of Women Voters (Box-folder 1-74)
- Va Comm College System 2 Way Telecon, Nov 14, 1986 (Box-folder 1-75)
- NUTN teleconference - Zallen October 1, 1987 (Box-folder 1-76)
- USDA Teleconf Ext, 10/16/86 (Box-folder 1-77)
- Extension Teleconference Shirley Gerkin, 9/15/86 (Box-folder 1-78)
- Geriatrics Teleconference VCU, June 1986 (Box-folder 1-79)
- Social Services Teleconf, 3/86 - 5/86 (Box-folder 1-80)
- Governor's Teleconference, 3/27/86 (Box-folder 1-81)
- Vet Medecine Teleconf, 10/13/85 (Box-folder 1-82)
- IRS Teleconf, Dec. 1984 (Box-folder 1-83)
- Va Tech Extension - VALUE Teleconference (Box-folder 1-84)
- Teleconference '82, 1989 (Box-folder 1-85)
- Misc E (Box-folder 2-1)
- E.S.M (Box-folder 2-1)
- Extension Va Tech (Box-folder 2-3)
- Misc F (Box-folder 2-4)
- Misc G (Box-folder 2-5)
- Geography Project (Box-folder 2-6)
- Graduate School (Box-folder 2-7)
- Misc H (Box-folder 2-8)
- Heterick Financial Info (Box-folder 2-9)
- Misc I (Box-folder 2-10)
- Information Systems Facility Program (Box-folder 2-11)
- Information Systems (Box-folder 2-12)
- Information Service (Box-folder 2-13)
- VPI equipment inventory system (Box-folder 2-14)
- Misc K (Box-folder 2-15)
- Misc L (Box-folder 2-16)
- Leadership Adv. Board VT (Box-folder 2-17)
- Library (Box-folder 2-18)
- Misc M (Box-folder 2-19)
- Misc N (Box-folder 2-20)
- National University of the AIR (Box-folder 2-21)
- North American Distance Education Group (Box-folder 2-22)
- NSU/Tech Visit (Box-folder 2-23)
- Misc P (Box-folder 2-24)
- Misc - Hand Out (Box-folder 2-25)
- Huffman - President Elect (Box-folder 2-26)
- Hufffman - President (Corres-1) (Box-folder 2-27)
- Huffman - President (Corres-2) (Box-folder 2-28)
- Huffman Past President (Box-folder 2-29)
- Learn-MGT-LRC ORG (Box-folder 2-30)
- Univ Slide Services (Box-folder 2-31)
- Didactron (Box-folder 2-32)
- Communication Technology Seminar Correspondence (Box-folder 3-1)
- AECT General 1986 (Box-folder 3-2)
- AECT General (Past) (Box-folder 3-3)
- AECT General 1981 (Box-folder 3-4)
- AECT Affiliate Relation (Box-folder 3-5)
- SRMLC (Box-folder 3-6)
- VEMA Correspondence (Box-folder 3-7)
- Huffman - Leadership Conf (Box-folder 3-8)
- VEMA Correspondence 1980 (Box-folder 3-9)
- VEMA Correspondence 1975-78 (Box-folder 3-10)
- LRC Staff Minutes (Box-folder 3-11)
- LRC Organizational Chart (Box-folder 3-12)
- LRC Annual Reports 71-83, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 3-13)
- Administration & Faculty - LRC (Box-folder 3-14)
- Activities Reports - Faculty, LRC (Box-folder 3-15)
- LRC Activities 71 - 77, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 3-16)
- AECT Photos (Box-folder 3-17)
- trulove I Stan Huffman 81-0092 (Box-folder 3-18)
- Stan Huffman 81-1560 (Box-folder 3-19)
- LRC External Evaluation, 4/26-4/28 1976 (Box-folder 3-20)
- Learning Resource Center Committee (Box-folder 3-21)
- WBRA Microwave Contrast (Box-folder 3-22)
- Telecommunication 1980- (Box-folder 3-23)
- TV Distribution System (VPI & SU) (Box-folder 3-24)
- Virginia Public Telecommunications Board Grant Proposal (Box-folder 3-25)
- Telecommunications Ad Hoc Committee (Inactive) (Box-folder 3-26)
- WBRA (Box-folder 3-27)
- Telecommunications (inactive) VPTC Satellite (Box-folder 3-28)
- Telecommunications Master Plan 1978 (Box-folder 3-29)
- Blacksburg Cable TV Telecommunications (Box-folder 3-30)
- Telecommunications VPTC Prison Project (Box-folder 4-1)
- Burruss Hall Auditorium (Box-folder 4-2)
- Bureau Teaching Materials (Box-folder 4-3)
- Agreements For Release of Audio and Video Taped Box Material (Box-folder 4-4)
- Extension Office Planning (Scheman 1976-77), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4-5)
- Alumni Slide Presentations Script (Box-folder 4-6)
- Faculty Development Other (Box-folder 4-7)
- Proposal General Electric Foundation (Box-folder 4-8)
- Higher Education TITLE VI - 1976 -77, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4-9)
- Misc "A" (Box-folder 4-10)
- Affirmative Action & EEO (Box-folder 4-11)
- Affirmative Action -- VPI & SU (Box-folder 4-12)
- A.E.C.T. (Box-folder 4-13)
- Alpha Phi Omega (Box-folder 4-14)
- Misc "B" (Box-folder 4-15)
- Misc "C" (Box-folder 4-16)
- Continuing Education Guidelines (non-credit programs) (Box-folder 4-17)
- Continuing Ed. Rep Group (Box-folder 4-18)
- Center for Innovative Technology -- VA (Box-folder 4-19)
- College of Arts & Sciences (Box-folder 4-20)
- College of Agriculture (Box-folder 4-21)
- College of Agriculture International Program -- Student (Box-folder 4-22)
- College of Agriculture -- Master Program (Box-folder 4-23)
- College of Agriculture TV Show (Box-folder 4-24)
- College of Architecture (Box-folder 4-25)
- College of Business (Box-folder 4-26)
- College of Education (Box-folder 4-27)
- College of Engineering (Box-folder 4-28)
- College of Human Resources (Box-folder 4-29)
- College of Veterinary Medicine (Box-folder 4-30)
- Conf. -- AECT Orlando, Fla 2/13-17/91 (Box-folder 4-31)
- Conf. -- VEMA Norfolk Nov. 15-17, 1990 (Box-folder 4-32)
- Conf. -- Telecon X San Jose, Calif Nov. 5-7, 1990 (Box-folder 4-33)
- Conf. -- Nicate Visit 10/7-10/90 Cleveland, Tenn (Box-folder 4-34)
- Conf. -- Telecourse Conference Miami, Fla October 11-13, 1990 (Box-folder 4-35)
- Conf. -- Puerto Rico Conference Sept 12, 1990 (Box-folder 4-36)
- Conf. -- NVTN Conference Sept. 26-28, 90 (Box-folder 4-37)
- Conf. -- Intercom '90 Film/Video Festival (Box-folder 4-38)
- Conf. -- NUTN Summer Conference July 24-27, 1990 Utah (Box-folder 4-39)
- Intelemart -- Washington, DC 6/11-14/90 (Box-folder 4-40)
- Dallas July 6-7, 1989, Elec. Delivery of Credit Programming (Box-folder 4-41)
- Agriculture Dean's conference, April 17, 1990 CEC (Box-folder 4-42)
- Satellites & Education Conference III, March 15-17, 1989, West Chester University (Box-folder 4-43)
- Telecon IX San Jose, Calif, October 1989 (Box-folder 4-44)
- NUTN Conference, Oct. 21-22, San Jose, California (Box-folder 4-45)
- Cooperative Ventures II Jekyll Island, March 8-10, 90 (Box-folder 5-1)
- AECT 1/31 to 2/4/90, Anaheim, Calif (Box-folder 5-2)
- SRMLC June 1-3, 1990, Orlando, Fla (Box-folder 5-3)
- Technology Conference -- Main, Sept. 1989 (Box-folder 5-4)
- Marketing Meetings, 5/30-6/1/90, St. Petersburg, Fla (Box-folder 5-5)
- National Center for Telecommunications & Information Policy (Box-folder 5-6)
- Using Media for Learning -- Bound Copies (Box-folder 5-7)
- Using Media for Learning -- Contracts & Distribution Correspondence (Box-folder 5-8)
- Using Media for Learning -- General Correspondence (Box-folder 5-9)
- Using Media for Learning -- Telecom. Grant, SAH (Box-folder 5-10)
- Trends (Box-folder 5-11)
- Learning Environments #19 (Box-folder 5-12)
- Games, Simulations, Computers (Box-folder 5-13)
- Community Resources #16 (Box-folder 5-14)
- Realia (Box-folder 5-15)
- Multimedia Script (Box-folder 5-16)
- Audio (Box-folder 5-17)
- Graphic Design (Box-folder 5-18)
- Motion Pictures -- Kath. (Box-folder 5-19)
- Film & Video Techniques -- Kath. (Box-folder 5-20)
- Television -- Kath. (Box-folder 5-21)
- Display #8 (Box-folder 5-22)
- Still Pics & Photos (Box-folder 5-23)
- Introduction to Media #1 (Box-folder 5-24)
- Graphics (Box-folder 5-25)
- Scripts -- Overheads, Lettering (Box-folder 5-26)
- Film & Video Techniques (Box-folder 5-27)
- Overhead Projection (Box-folder 5-28)
- Lettering (Box-folder 5-29)
- Realia, Models,& Demonstrations (Box-folder 5-30)
- Photography & Still Pics (Box-folder 5-31)
- Planning/Producing Multi-Media Programs (Box-folder 5-32)
- Motion Pictures (Box-folder 5-33)
- Instructional Technology for Adult Learning (Box-folder 5-34)
- Photography & Still Pictures (Box-folder 5-35)
- Motion Pic., TV & Film & Video Scripts Original (Box-folder 5-36)
- Display (Box-folder 5-37)
- Learning & Communication #2 (Box-folder 5-38)
- Print & Non Print (Box-folder 5-39)
- Releases -- Blacksburg (Box-folder 5-40)
- Virginia Tech Employees & Students Releases (Box-folder 5-41)
- Release Forms -- Salem, Andrew Lewis (Box-folder 5-42)
- Releases -- Cave Spring High (Box-folder 5-43)
- Fleming High -- Roanoke (Box-folder 5-44)
- Virginia Heights -- Roanoke City Release (Box-folder 5-45)
- Westside -- Roanoke Elementary (Box-folder 5-46)
- Release Forms -- Winchester Public (Box-folder 5-47)
- Mrs. Pitts Permission Slips, Frances Elementary -- Richmond (Box-folder 5-48)
- Frances Elementary -- Richmond (Box-folder 5-49)
- Glencoe Elementary -- Roanoke Releases (Box-folder 5-50)
- Henderson Middle (Box-folder 5-51)
- Monterey Elemen. Roanoke City (Box-folder 5-52)
- Releases Northside High School Roanoke (Box-folder 6-1)
- Northside Middle School -- Roanoke Releases (Box-folder 6-2)
- Richmond -- City Hall & John Marshall (Box-folder 6-3)
- Waiver Letters (Box-folder 6-4)
- Release Forms Fishburne (Box-folder 6-5)
- Using Media for Learning -- PR Releases (Box-folder 6-6)
- Using Media for Learning Originals (Box-folder 6-7)
- Project -- General Info (Box-folder 6-8)
- Photos & Negatives -- Pt. 1 (Box-folder 6-9)
- Photos & Negatives -- Pt. 2 (Box-folder 6-10)
- PSSC Planning 1990 (Box-folder 6-11)
- PSSC -- NCTIP (Box-folder 6-12)
- SRMLC (Box-folder 6-13)
- Purchasing Information (Box-folder 6-14)
- Misc. "R" (Box-folder 6-15)
- Risk Management (Box-folder 6-16)
- Misc. "S" (Box-folder 6-17)
- Surplus (Box-folder 6-18)
- Misc. "T" (Box-folder 6-19)
- Telecommunications -- General (Box-folder 6-20)
- Teleconference Planning (Box-folder 6-21)
- Teleconference Pricing (Box-folder 6-22)
- Telephones (Box-folder 6-23)
- Travel Information (Box-folder 6-24)
- United Fund (Box-folder 6-25)
- Misc. "U" (Box-folder 6-26)
- Misc. "V" (Box-folder 6-27)
- VPI & SU Faculty & Campus Info. 1975 - (Box-folder 6-28)
- Misc. W (Box-folder 6-29)
- Western Region Consortium Media Committee (Box-folder 6-30)
- Western Region Consortium General Info. (Box-folder 6-31)
- Huffman -- Resume" (Box-folder 6-32)
- Instructional Media -- Communication & Learning (Box-folder 6-33)
- Instructional Media -- Selection & Utilization (Box-folder 6-34)
- Instructional Media -- Graphics (Box-folder 6-35)
- Instructional Media -- Overhead Projection (Box-folder 6-36)
- Instructional Media -- Slides & Filmstrips (Box-folder 6-37)
- Instructional Media -- Opaque Projection (Box-folder 6-38)
- Instructional Media -- Chalkboards (Box-folder 6-39)
- Instructional Media -- Bulletin Boards (Box-folder 6-40)
- Instructional Media -- Feltboards (Box-folder 6-41)
- Instructional Media -- Exhibits (Box-folder 6-42)
- Instructional Media -- Audio Devices (Box-folder 6-43)
- Instructional Media -- Motion Pictures (Box-folder 6-44)
- Instructional Media -- Television (Box-folder 6-45)
- Instructional Media -- Models & Realia (Box-folder 6-46)
- Instructional Media -- Maps & Globes (Box-folder 6-47)
- Instructional Media -- Community Resources (Box-folder 6-48)
- Instructional Media -- Flat Pictures (Box-folder 6-49)
- Instructional Media -- Photography (Box-folder 6-50)
- Instructional Media -- Programed Learning (Box-folder 6-51)
- Instructional Media -- Equipment (Box-folder 6-52)
- Instructional Media -- Administration & Facilities (Box-folder 6-53)
- Slide Productions -- SAH (Box-folder 7-1)
- Sound System Advisory Committee (Box-folder 7-2)
- Smyth Hall (Box-folder 7-3)
- SREB Southern Regional Education Board (Box-folder 7-4)
- Southern Regional Faculty & Instructional Development Consortium (Box-folder 7-5)
- Technology Speech (Box-folder 7-6)
- Technology Transfer Council (Box-folder 7-7)
- Dept. of Information Technology -- Virginia Telemedia Systems (Box-folder 7-8)
- Dept. of Information Technology -- Satellite Technology Applications (Box-folder 7-9)
- Dept. of Information Technology -- Engineering Program Operations Handbook (Box-folder 7-10)
- Telecommunications Advisory Group -- TAG (Box-folder 7-11)
- Telecommunications Advisory Group -- Personnel Study (Box-folder 7-12)
- Telecommunications Subcommittee of University Computer Committee (Box-folder 7-13)
- Teleconference Extension Policy (Box-folder 7-14)
- Animal Science Requisitions (Box-folder 7-15)
- New Buildings -- 1987 (Box-folder 7-16)
- Vet School Planning (Box-folder 7-17)
- Architecture/Engineering Bldg (Box-folder 7-18)
- Western Virginia Media Consortium (Box-folder 7-19)
- Woodrow Wilson College (Box-folder 7-20)
- World Futures Society (Box-folder 7-21)
- AECT Summer Conference, (August 1-6, 1989) Blacksburg (Box-folder 7-22)
- NUTN Originators Conference, July 18-21,1989, CEC (Box-folder 7-23)
- VEMA Leadership Conf. CEC, 7/9-10/89 (Box-folder 7-24)
- University Copyright Committee -- Pt. 1 (Box-folder 7-25)
- University Copyright Committee -- Pt. 2 (Box-folder 7-26)
- University Copyright Committee -- Pt. 3 (Box-folder 7-27)
- Financial & Faculty Ephemera (Box-folder 7-28)
- Administrators Conference (Box-folder 7-29)
- Alumni Association (Box-folder 7-30)
- Ampex 1986 (Box-folder 7-31)
- Catalog -- University (Box-folder 7-32)
- CEC Renovation (Box-folder 7-33)
- CIP Center for Interactive Programs -- University of Wisconsin Ext. (Box-folder 7-34)
- Center for Volunteer Development (Box-folder 7-35)
- Commencement -- General (Box-folder 7-36)
- Governor's School -- Roanoke (Box-folder 7-37)
- Human Society Project (Box-folder 8-1)
- Intellectual Properties Committee (Box-folder 8-2)
- Copyright University TV Rights & Responsibilities (Box-folder 8-3)
- Haralick: Gypsy Proposal (Box-folder 8-4)
- Forest Products Investment Model (Box-folder 8-5)
- Kamat IBM PC Software Package (Box-folder 8-6)
- Roach/Guess/1 (Box-folder 8-7)
- Electromagnetics Program -- Warren Stutzman (Box-folder 8-8)
- PSSC Membership Info. (Box-folder 8-9)
- PSSC Board of Directors -- Papers (Box-folder 8-10)
- PSSC Board of Directors -- Consortium Books (Box-folder 8-11)
- PSSC (Box-folder 8-12)
- Nuclear Winter Program (Box-folder 8-13)
- NUTN: National University Teleconference Network -- Pt. 1 (Box-folder 8-14)
- NUTN: National University Teleconference Network -- Pt. 2 (Box-folder 8-15)
- Proposal Correspondence -- General (Box-folder 8-16)
- Exxon Education Foundation Proposals (Box-folder 8-17)
- Civil War Project 1981 (Box-folder 8-18)
- The Civil War in Virginia (Box-folder 8-19)
- The Civil War in Virginia -- Ephemera (Box-folder 8-20)
- Satellite Project, 1977 (Box-folder 8-21)
- New Satellite Project '82 (Box-folder 8-22)
- 1986-87 Self-Study -- University, Pt. 1 (Box-folder 8-24)
- 1986-87 Self-Study -- University, Pt. 2 (Box-folder 8-24)
- 1984 Self-Study (Box-folder 8-25)